{
  "apikey": "%PUT-YOUR-API-KEY-HERE%",
  "description": "This is simple calibration data used for testing purposes. Do not use it in production environment!",
  "copyright": "Copyright (C) 2238 by BanAN Technologies Inc.",
  "test-data": [
    {
      "question": "30 + 20",
      "answer": 50
    },
    {
      "question": "53 + 93",
      "answer": 146
    },
    {
      "question": "36 + 82",
      "answer": 118
    },
    {
      "question": "80 + 8",
      "answer": 88
    },
    {
      "question": "15 + 90",
      "answer": 105
    },
    {
      "question": "70 + 55",
      "answer": 125
    },
    {
      "question": "11 + 87",
      "answer": 98
    },
    {
      "question": "28 + 35",
      "answer": 63
    },
    {
      "question": "89 + 42",
      "answer": 131
    },
    {
      "question": "95 + 92",
      "answer": 187
    },
    {
      "question": "69 + 5",
      "answer": 74
    },
    {
      "question": "38 + 14",
      "answer": 52
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 61",
      "answer": 71
    },
    {
      "question": "69 + 20",
      "answer": 89
    },
    {
      "question": "42 + 29",
      "answer": 71
    },
    {
      "question": "36 + 90",
      "answer": 126
    },
    {
      "question": "4 + 99",
      "answer": 103
    },
    {
      "question": "74 + 70",
      "answer": 144
    },
    {
      "question": "59 + 27",
      "answer": 86
    },
    {
      "question": "58 + 47",
      "answer": 105
    },
    {
      "question": "44 + 38",
      "answer": 82
    },
    {
      "question": "51 + 93",
      "answer": 144
    },
    {
      "question": "39 + 78",
      "answer": 117
    },
    {
      "question": "2 + 3",
      "answer": 5
    },
    {
      "question": "36 + 39",
      "answer": 75
    },
    {
      "question": "54 + 87",
      "answer": 141
    },
    {
      "question": "52 + 37",
      "answer": 89
    },
    {
      "question": "51 + 56",
      "answer": 107
    },
    {
      "question": "93 + 82",
      "answer": 175
    },
    {
      "question": "44 + 11",
      "answer": 55
    },
    {
      "question": "94 + 71",
      "answer": 165
    },
    {
      "question": "92 + 75",
      "answer": 167
    },
    {
      "question": "94 + 38",
      "answer": 132
    },
    {
      "question": "99 + 4",
      "answer": 103
    },
    {
      "question": "51 + 73",
      "answer": 124
    },
    {
      "question": "4 + 19",
      "answer": 23
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 84",
      "answer": 93
    },
    {
      "question": "85 + 80",
      "answer": 165
    },
    {
      "question": "81 + 47",
      "answer": 128
    },
    {
      "question": "80 + 56",
      "answer": 136
    },
    {
      "question": "96 + 1",
      "answer": 97
    },
    {
      "question": "33 + 62",
      "answer": 95
    },
    {
      "question": "26 + 21",
      "answer": 47
    },
    {
      "question": "54 + 18",
      "answer": 72
    },
    {
      "question": "39 + 49",
      "answer": 88
    },
    {
      "question": "25 + 56",
      "answer": 81
    },
    {
      "question": "83 + 26",
      "answer": 109
    },
    {
      "question": "64 + 23",
      "answer": 87
    },
    {
      "question": "24 + 10",
      "answer": 34
    },
    {
      "question": "72 + 17",
      "answer": 89
    },
    {
      "question": "28 + 94",
      "answer": 122
    },
    {
      "question": "46 + 60",
      "answer": 106
    },
    {
      "question": "89 + 45",
      "answer": 134
    },
    {
      "question": "28 + 83",
      "answer": 111
    },
    {
      "question": "11 + 94",
      "answer": 105
    },
    {
      "question": "23 + 94",
      "answer": 117
    },
    {
      "question": "30 + 31",
      "answer": 61
    },
    {
      "question": "71 + 86",
      "answer": 157
    },
    {
      "question": "46 + 9",
      "answer": 55
    },
    {
      "question": "69 + 34",
      "answer": 103
    },
    {
      "question": "100 + 35",
      "answer": 135
    },
    {
      "question": "41 + 100",
      "answer": 141
    },
    {
      "question": "17 + 21",
      "answer": 38
    },
    {
      "question": "49 + 29",
      "answer": 78
    },
    {
      "question": "87 + 5",
      "answer": 92
    },
    {
      "question": "53 + 32",
      "answer": 85
    },
    {
      "question": "57 + 40",
      "answer": 97
    },
    {
      "question": "61 + 95",
      "answer": 156
    },
    {
      "question": "27 + 90",
      "answer": 117
    },
    {
      "question": "33 + 76",
      "answer": 109
    },
    {
      "question": "78 + 41",
      "answer": 119
    },
    {
      "question": "49 + 13",
      "answer": 62
    },
    {
      "question": "46 + 40",
      "answer": 86
    },
    {
      "question": "48 + 41",
      "answer": 89
    },
    {
      "question": "31 + 25",
      "answer": 56
    },
    {
      "question": "41 + 87",
      "answer": 128
    },
    {
      "question": "51 + 43",
      "answer": 94
    },
    {
      "question": "94 + 90",
      "answer": 184
    },
    {
      "question": "3 + 22",
      "answer": 25
    },
    {
      "question": "68 + 85",
      "answer": 153
    },
    {
      "question": "33 + 76",
      "answer": 109
    },
    {
      "question": "100 + 58",
      "answer": 158
    },
    {
      "question": "74 + 77",
      "answer": 151
    },
    {
      "question": "23 + 13",
      "answer": 36
    },
    {
      "question": "42 + 32",
      "answer": 74
    },
    {
      "question": "26 + 28",
      "answer": 54
    },
    {
      "question": "32 + 56",
      "answer": 88
    },
    {
      "question": "35 + 77",
      "answer": 112
    },
    {
      "question": "23 + 20",
      "answer": 43
    },
    {
      "question": "21 + 34",
      "answer": 55
    },
    {
      "question": "51 + 49",
      "answer": 100
    },
    {
      "question": "34 + 25",
      "answer": 59
    },
    {
      "question": "60 + 65",
      "answer": 125
    },
    {
      "question": "68 + 84",
      "answer": 152
    },
    {
      "question": "26 + 44",
      "answer": 70
    },
    {
      "question": "7 + 46",
      "answer": 53
    },
    {
      "question": "74 + 49",
      "answer": 123
    },
    {
      "question": "85 + 30",
      "answer": 115
    },
    {
      "question": "76 + 43",
      "answer": 119
    },
    {
      "question": "84 + 83",
      "answer": 167
    }
  ],
  "chunk": {
    "number": 16,
    "total": 22,
    "size": 100,
    "range": {
      "from": 1500,
      "to": 1600
    }
  }
}